Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Organizations PE.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- S, 1885-2012; 12.75 Linear Feet in 12 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 oversize shared box
  - Sozialdemokratische Schulverins Zurich, undated (Box 96)
  - Sozialistische Arbeiter Partie (Germany), 1932, undated (Box 96)
  - Sozialistische Arbeiter Partie von Nord Amerika (Philadelphia, PA), 1889 (Box 96)
  - Sozialistische Arbeiterjugend (Germany), 1923 (Box 96)
  - Sozialistische Arbeiterjugend (Germany), 1932, undated (Box 96)
  - Sozialistische Einheitspartie Deutschlands I, 1946-1971 (Box 96)
  - Sozialistische Einheitspartie Deutschlands II, 1946-1971 (Box 96)
  - Sozialistische Partie Osterreichs (Austria), 1945-1958 (Box 96)
  - Sozialistischen Bundes, undated (Box 96)
  - Sozialdemokratischenpartei der Stadt Bern, undated (Box 96)
  - Spanish Atrocities Committee (Great Britain), 1897 (Box 96)
  - Spanish Committee of Liberation (New York, NY), 1945 (Box 96)
  - Spanish Embassy in London, 1936-1937, undated (Box 96)
  - Spanish Embassy (Washington, DC), 1945-1949 (Box 96)
  - Spanish Ex-Servicemen's Association (London, U.K.), 1960 (Box 96)
  - Spanish Information Bureau, undated (Box 96)
  - Spanish Intellectual Aid (New York, NY), 1939 (Box 96)
  - Spanish Refugee Aid, 1962-1988 (Box Shared Tamiment 189, Folder 23)
  - Spanish Village Court, undated (Box 96)
  - Spark: A New School Student Organization (New York, NY), undated (Box 96)
  - Sparks Fly Committee: East Coast, 1998 (Box 96)
  - Spartacist Forum, 2007 (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Spartacist League of Australia and New Zealand, 1970 (Box 96)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S., 1964-1968 (Box 96)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S. I, 1967-1969 (Box 96)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S. II, 1967-1969 (Box 96)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S. I, 1970-1971 (Box 96)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S. II, 1970-1971 (Box 97)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S., 1972-1980 (Box 97)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S., 1981- (Box 97)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S., undated (Box 97)
  - Spartacist Publishing Company, 1970- (Box 97)
  - Spartacus Youth Club (New York University), 1997, undated (Box 97)
  - Spartacus Youth League, 1935-1936 (Box 97)
  - Spartacus Youth League of America I, 1968, undated (Box 97)
  - Spartacus Youth League of America II, 1968-, undated (Box 97)
  - Speak Out! (San Francisco, CA), 1994, undated (Box 97, Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Speak Out and Demonstrate Against Reaganism (Hilton Hotel, New York, NY), circa 1982 (Box 97)
  - Speculator, the, 1984 (Box 97)
  - Spread Magazine, 2009- (Box 97)
  - Spring Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1967 (Box 97)
  - Springfield Co-Operative Society, 1917-1918 (Box 97)
  - Springfield Movement for a Democratic Society, 1969 (Box 97)
  - St. Louis Emergency Defense Committee, 1950s (Box 97)
  - St. Louis Labor (St. Louis, MO), 1902 (Box 97)
  - St. Mark's Church in-the-Bowery (New York, NY): Community Documentation Workshop (Oral Histories), 1979- (Box 97)
  - Stage and Arena Guild of America, 1958 (Box 97)
  - Stage for Action, 1947 (Box 97)
  - Stand Up New York, 2002 (Box 97)
  - Standing Joint Pacifist Committee (Great Britain), 1957 (Box 97)
  - State Charities Aid Association (New York, NY), 1912 (Box 97)
  - State Commission Against Discrimination (New York), undated (Box 97)
  - State Publishing Company: Pamphlets, 1954, undated (Box 97)
  - State Workingmen's Assembly, 1894-1905 (Box 97)
  - Steve Wilson Books: Catalog, undated (Box 97)
  - Stiftung Archiv der Parteien und Massenorganisationen der DDR im Bundesarchiv, 2000- (Box 97)
  - Still We Rise Coalition, 2004 (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - Stockholm Conference on Vietnam, 1970 (Box 97)
  - Stockholm International Peace Research Institute, 1975 (Box 97)
  - Stockholm Peace Appeal Campaign, undated (Box 97)
  - Stony Brook Student Defense Fund, undated (Box 97)
  - Stop Omega Campaign (Australia), 1974 (Box 97)
  - Stop the Draft Week Committee, undated (Box 97)
  - Stop U.S. Tax-Funded Aid to Israel Now (SUSTAIN campaign), 2002 (Box 97)
  - Straight Talk Pamphlets, 1978 (Box 97)
  - Strangers in a Tangled Wilderness, 2009- (Box 97)
  - Straphangers United! (New York, NY), 1960- (Box 97)
  - Street Transvestites Action Revolutionaries (STAR), undated (Box 97)
  - Street Transvestites for Gay Power, 1970 (Box 97)
  - Streetwork, undated (Box 97)
  - Strong, Sturgis and Co, 1916 (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Struggle for Freedom, undated (Box 97)
  - Student and Youth Solidarity Movement, undated (Box 129, Folder 21)
  - Student Coalition Against the Death Penalty, undated (Box 97)
  - Student Committee for Algerian Freedom, 1958 (Box 97)
  - Student Committee for Miners, 1963 (Box 97)
  - Student Committee for Travel to Cuba (New York, NY), undated (Box 97)
  - Student Committee on Progressive Education (New York, NY), 1960, undated (Box 97)
  - Student Committee to Elect Mark Lane, 1962 (Box 97)
  - Student Congress Against War (Chicago, IL), 1932 (Box 97)
  - Student Faculty Organizing Committee, 1968 (Box 97)
  - Student / Farmworker Alliance, 2002 (Box 97)
  - Student Free Speech Defense Fund, 1964 (Box 97)
  - Student Labor Action Project (SLAP), 2001-, undated (Box 97)
  - Student Liberation Action Movement (New York, NY), circa 1971 (Box 97)
  - Student Liberation Action Movement (New York, NY), 1998-1999, undated (Box 97)
  - Student Mobilization Committee, 1968-1970s (Box 97, Box 129, Folder 19)
  - Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1968, undated (Box 97)
  - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee I, 1961-1970 (Box 97)
  - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee II, 1961-1970 (Box 97)
  - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee III, 1961-1970 (Box 97)
  - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee IV, 1961-1970 (Box 97)
  - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee V, 1961-1970 (Box 97)
  - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee: Mississippi Project Parents Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 97)
  - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee: Mississippi Summer Project, 1964-1965 (Box 97)
  - Student Peace Action Network, undated (Box 98)
  - Student Peace Union, 1959 (Box 98)
  - Student Peace Union, 1960 (Box 98)
  - Student Peace Union I, 1961 (Box 98)
  - Student Peace Union II, 1961 (Box 98)
  - Student Peace Union, 1962 (Box 98)
  - Student Peace Union, 1963 (Box 98)
  - Student Peace Union, 1964 (Box 98)
  - Student Peace Union, 1965-1966 (Box 98)
  - Student Peace Union, undated (Box 98)
  - Student Strike Support Committee (Yale University), 1977 (Box 98)
  - Student Syndicalist League, circa 1974 (Box 98)
  - Student Union for Peace Action (Toronto, CAN), 1960-1966 (Box 98)
  - Student Union for Peace and Justice (Los Angeles, CA), undated (Box 98)
  - Students and Youth for a People's Peace, 1971 (Box 98)
  - Students Against Testing, circa 2002- (Box 98)
  - Students Against Sweatshops, undated (Box 98)
  - Students Against War (New York, NY), undated (Box 98)
  - Students and Youth Against Racism (New York, NY), circa 1983 (Box 98)
  - Student's Cooperative Institute (Brooklyn, NY), 1919, 1945 (Box 98)
  - Students Creating Radical Change, 2008- (Box 98)
  - Students for a Democratic Society, undated (Box 98)
  - Students for Democratic Action I, 1947-1958 (Box 98, Box 129, Folder 18)
  - Students for Democratic Action II, 1947-1958 (Box 98)
  - Students for Economic Democracy, 1980- (Box 98)
  - Students for Human Rights, 1970 (Box 98)
  - Students for Justice in Palestine, 2005, undated (Box 98)
  - Students for Social Equality, 2001-2003 (Box 98, Box 129, Folder 20)
  - Student Struggle for Soviet Jewry, undated (Box 99)
  - Study Group on China Policy, 1966 (Box 98)
  - Study Group on East European Questions, circa 1964 (Box 98)
  - S.U. Anarchist Group, 1975 (Box 98)
  - Substitutes United for Better Schools (Chicago, IL), 1978 (Box 98)
  - Sudenten Social Democratic Party, circa 1944 (Box 98)
  - Summer School for Office Workers I, 1935-1949 (Box 98)
  - Summer School for Office Workers II, 1935-1949 (Box 98)
  - Summer School for Women Workers in Industry (Pomona, NY), 1929-1935 (Box 98)
  - Sunrise Book Collective, 1977 (Box 98)
  - Sunya Peace Project (SUNY-Albany), 1987-1988 (Box 98)
  - Support Daniel, circa 2012 (Box 98)
  - Survival of American Indians Association, 1965- (Box 98)
  - Survival Task Force (of City College), undated (Box 98)
  - Surrealist Movement in the United States, 2002 (Box 98)
  - Swedish Social Democratic Labor Party, 1944- (Box 98)
  - Swarthmore College: Peace Collection, 1980 (Box 98)
  - Sweat: Independent Labor Magazine of North America, 1977- (Box 98)
  - Sweatshop Watch (Oakland, CA), 2002 (Box 98)
  - Swift and Company Employes Benefit Association, 1907 (Box 98)
  - Sydney South for Workers Action, 1970 (Box 98)
  - Sylvis Society, 1984 (Box 98)
  - Syracuse Cultural Workers Project, 2001- (Box 98)
  - Syracuse Peace Council, 1972-, 2007, undated (Box 98)
  - Szocialdemokrata Part (Hungary), 1904 (Box 98)
- T, 1895-2012; 3.5 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - T. Tait Memorial Committee (Edinburgh, Scotland): Pamphlet, circa 1941 (Box 98)
  - Take Back NYU!, 2008- (Box 98)
  - Take Back the Night, 1983- (Box 98)
  - Take Back the Strand, 2012 (Box 98)
  - Take New York City Out of the War Now!, undated (Box 98)
  - Talk with the People Campaign, 1972 (Box 98)
  - Taller Latinoamericano, 1984 (Box 98)
  - Tam-Arkiv - Tam Archives (Stockholm, Sweden), undated (Box 98)
  - Tamiment Institute, 1924-1952 (Box 98)
  - Tamiment Institute, 1953-1954 (Box 98)
  - Tamiment Institute, 1955 (Box 98)
  - Tamiment Institute, 1956-1959 (Box 98)
  - Tamiment Institute, 1960-1963 (Box 99)
  - Tamiment Institute, undated (Box 99)
  - Tamiment Library I, 1969-2007 (Box 99, Box 129, Folder 22)
  - Tamiment Library II, 1969- (Box 99)
  - Tamiment Players, 1961, undated (Box 99)
  - Tamiment Playhouse, 1960 (Box 99)
  - Tapol (Indonesia), 1975- (Box 99)
  - Tax for Life Campaign, undated (Box 99)
  - Taxpayers Against War, 1967 (Box 99)
  - Teachers Committee for Peace in Vietnam, 1966- (Box 99)
  - Teachers Concerned About Vietnam, 1967 (Box 99)
  - Teachers Defense Committee, 1954, undated (Box 99)
  - Teachers for a Democratic Society, 1960- (Box 99)
  - Teachers' League for Academic Freedom (New York, NY), 1935 (Box 99)
  - Teachers' Research Council, undated (Box 99)
  - Technocracy, Inc. (New York, NY), 1934- (Box 99)
  - Tell us the Truth Tour, 2000- (Box 99)
  - Temporary Committee on World Organization, undated (Box 99)
  - Temporary Organizing Committee for a Marxist-Leninist Youth Organization, undated (Box 99)
  - Temporary Organizing Committee for a Revolutionary Working Class Youth Organization, 1969, undated (Box 99)
  - Temps Nouveaux (Paris, France: 1895), undated (Box 99)
  - Tenant Action Group (Philadelphia, PA), undated (Box 99)
  - Tenants' League of Philadelphia, 1940 (Box 99)
  - Tenants' Party, 1974- (Box 99)
  - Tennessee Tombigee Waterway Mesbic Fund, undated (Box 99)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority I, 1937- (Box 99)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority II, 1937- (Box 99)
  - Tenth Street Residents Opposed to the War in Vietnam, 1967 (Box 99)
  - Terrorist Information Project, 1974 (Box 99)
  - Terzani Defense Committee, 1929 (Box 99)
  - Texas Farm Workers Support Committee, 1977 (Box 99)
  - Theaters Against War, 2010 (Box 99)
  - Theatre Arts Committee, 1938 (Box 99)
  - Theatre Festival (R.S.F.S.R.) (Moscow-Leningrad), 1936 (Box 99)
  - Theatre for the New City, 1983- (Box 99)
  - Theatre Union (New York, NY), circa 1934 (Box 99)
  - Theodore Dreiser Cultural Workshop (New York, NY), 1940- (Box 99)
  - Think Outside the Bomb, 2010- (Box 99)
  - Third International, 1951 (Box 129, Folder 23)
  - Third World Coalition, 1978- (Box 99)
  - Third World Gay Revolution, 1970 (Box 99)
  - Third World Newsreel: Labor Films, 1980 (Box 99)
  - Third World Task Force, 1971 (Box 99)
  - Third World Trade Union Congress, 1953 (Box 99)
  - Third World Women's Archives, 1983 (Box 99)
  - Third World Women for Abortion Law Repeal, undated (Box 99)
  - Thomas and Maurer Committee of One Hundred Thousand (New York, NY), 1932 (Box 99)
  - Thomas and Nelson Independent Committee (New York, NY), 1936- (Box 99)
  - Thomas Paine Independent Democratic Club, undated (Box 129, Folder 24)
  - Three Arrows, 1986 (Box 99)
  - Three Arrows Press (New York, NY), 1949- (Box 99)
  - Tiamat, 1978 (Box 99)
  - Tianguis Tlaloc, 1999 (Box 99)
  - Tidsskrift Centret (Denmark), undated (Box 99)
  - Times Change Press (New York, NY), 1972- (Box 99)
  - Times Up!, 2000- (Box 99)
  - Toldeo Youth for Soviet Jewry, undated (Box 99)
  - Tom Mooney Molders Defense Committee (Box 99)
  - Tom Paine School of Social Science (Philadelphia, PA), 1942- (Box 99)
  - Tompkins-Cortland Labor Coalition (Ithaca, NY), undated (Box 99)
  - Tompkins Square Housing Committee, 1963- (Box 99)
  - Tompkins Square Neighbors for Peace Action, undated (Box 99)
  - Tompkins Square Peace Center Committee, 1962 (Box 99)
  - Toward Freedom (Burlington, VT), 1990 (Box 99)
  - Toward Freedom (Chicago, IL), 1958 (Box 99)
  - Town Tenants' League (Great Britain), 1913 (Box 99)
  - Trade Union Action and Democracy, undated (Box 99)
  - Trade Union Art School, undated (Box 99)
  - Trade Union Centre for German Workers in Great Britain, 1942-1945 (Box 99)
  - Trade Union Committee 1959 May Day Celebration (New York, NY) (Box 99)
  - Trade Union Committee for the Freedom of Lieut. Gilbert (New York, NY), undated (Box 99)
  - Trade Union Committee on Anti-Labor Legislation, 1936 (Box 99)
  - Trade Union Committee to Defend Louis Weinstock, undated (Box 99)
  - Trade Union Committee to Repeal the Smith Act (San Francisco, CA), undated (Box 99)
  - Trade Union Conference for United Action, undated (Box 99)
  - Trade Union Defense Committee, 1950- (Box 99)
  - Trade Union Education Fund, undated (Box 99)
  - Trade Union Educational League, 1924-1927 (Box 99)
  - Trade Union Unity League, undated (Box 99)
    The Trade Union Unity League was the American section of the Red International Labor Union.
  - Trade Union Women's Seminar, 1974 (Box 99)
  - Trade Unionists for a Labor Party, undated (Box 99, Box 129, Folder 25)
  - Trade Unionists for Peace, 1966- (Box 99)
  - Tradeswoman, Inc., 2000- (Box 99)
  - Trail of Broken Treaties Caravan, 1972 (Box 99)
  - Trans-Atlantic Information Service, 1935- (Box 99)
  - Transcendental Students, 1969- (Box 99)
  - Transit Crisis Coalition (New York, NY), circa 1969 (Box 99)
  - Transnationals Information Exchange, undated (Box 99)
  - Treaty Campaign Fund (Pine Ridge Reservation, SD), 1984 (Box 99)
  - Trenton Coalition Against the War in the Middle East, undated (Box 99)
  - Trenton Committee on Latin America, undated (Box 99)
  - Tresca [Carlos] Memorial Committee (New York, NY), 1945- (Box 99)
  - Trevelyan House (Penzance, U.K.), undated (Box 99)
  - Tribune Publications (London, U.K.) I, 1950-1952 (Box 99)
    Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection of Oversized Material (PE 040) also contains a Tribune Publications file.
  - Tribune Publications (London, U.K.) II, 1950-1952 (Box 99)
  - Tricontinental Committee of Support to Vietnam, undated (Box 99)
  - Tricontinental News Service, 1972 (Box 99)
  - Troops Out Movement (London, U.K.), undated (Box 99)
  - Troops Out Now Coalition, 2005 (Box 99)
  - Trotzkistische Liga Deutschlands, 1976 (Box 129, Folder 26)
  - Trotskyist International Liaison Committee, 1982 (Box 99)
  - Trotskyist League (Canada), 1977 (Box 99)
  - Trotskyist Organization of the United States (Detroit, MI), 1976- (Box 99)
  - Trust Fund, Telephone Tax, undated (Box 99)
  - Turn Toward Peace (Seattle, WA), 1961- (Box 99)
  - Tucson Marxist-Leninist Collective, 1976- (Box 99)
  - Tucson Working Committee (Venice, CA), undated (Box 99)
  - Twentieth Century Fund, 1945- (Box 100)
  - Twin Cities Draft Information Center, 1969 (Box 100)
  - Twin Oaks Community, 1972 (Box 100)
  - Tyomies Eteenpain (Newspaper) (Superior, WI), circa 1985 (Box 100)
    Materials in this file are related to the 75th anniversary celebration of Tyomies Eteenpain, a Finnish-American newspaper.
  - Tyovaen Arkisto (Finland), 1999- (Box 100)
  - Tyovaenperinne-Arbetartadition (Labor Movement) (Finland), circa 1980s (Box 100)
- U, 1890-2010; 5.25 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes, 2 manuscript boxes, and 1 oversize shared box
  - UConn Gay Alliance, 1975 (Box 100)
  - UConn Medical Aid Committee, 1973 (Box 100)
  - Ukrainian American Fraternal Union, 1948- (Box 100)
  - Ukrainsak Partiia Sotsialistiv-Revoluitsioneriv, 1915 (Box 100)
  - UMass Boston Anti-War Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 100)
  - Unabhangige Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (Independent Social-Democratic Party of German), 1920 (Box 100)
  - Underground Press Syndicate, 1973 (Box 100)
  - Unemployed Councils of Boston, undated (Box 100)
  - Unemployed Councils of Cook County (Illinois), 1932 (Box 100)
  - Unemployed Council of New England, 1932 (Box 100)
  - Unemployed League (Lucas County, OH), undated (Box 100)
  - Unemployed Leagues of Greater New York, undated (Box 100)
  - Unemployed Union of New Jersey, 1933 (Box 100)
  - Unemployed Workers' Organizing Committee, undated (Box 100)
  - Unemployment and Poverty Action Committee, 2003 (Box 100)
  - Unified Communist Party of Nepal, circa 2010 (Box 100)
  - Union Committee Against Secret Service Harassment, 1980 (Box 100)
  - Union Committee of Unemployed People (Baltimore, MD), undated (Box 100)
  - Union Committee on the Rising Cost of Living, 1941 (Box 100)
  - Union Communication Services Inc. (USC, Inc.): Catalogs, undated (Box 100)
  - Union Cooperative Insurance Association, circa 1920s (Box 100)
  - Union Democracy in Action, 1961- (Box 100)
  - Union des Femmes Francaises, undated (Box 100)
  - Union for Democratic Action I, 1942 (Box 100)
  - Union for Democratic Action II, 1942- (Box 100)
  - Union for Democratic Action: Chicago Office, 1941- (Box 100)
  - Union for Democratic Action Educational Fund (U.S.), 1945- (Box 100)
  - Union for Democratic Socialism, 1952- (Box 100)
  - Union for Jobs or Income Now, undated (Box 100)
  - Union for National Draft Opposition, 1970- (Box 100)
  - Union for Radical Political Economics, 1971- (Box 100)
  - Union for Radical Political Economics, undated (Box 100)
  - Union Labor Life Insurance Co. I, 1925- (Box 100)
  - Union Labor Life Insurance Co. II, 1925- (Box 100)
  - Union Labor Life Insurance Co. III, 1925- (Box 100)
  - Union League Club: Committee on the Study of Bolshevism, 1919- (Box 100)
  - Union Leadership Academy, 1956- (Box 100)
  - Union Minorities and Women Leadership Training Project, 1979 (Box 100)
  - Union of American Exiles in Britain: Serial, 1972 (Box 100)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists, 1975- (Box 100)
  - Union of Democratic Control, 1919- (Box 100)
  - Union Labor Legionnaires: National Conference, 1946- (Box 100)
  - Union of the Radicals of North America, undated (Box 100)
  - Union of the Struggle for the Liberation of the Peoples of Russia (SBONR) (Munich, Germany), 1957 (Box 100)
  - Union of Times Thieves Local #00, 2000- (Box 100)
  - Union of Vietnam Women in France, 1948 (Box 100)
  - Union Party, undated (Box 100)
  - Union Patriotique (Haiti), 1921 (Box 100)
  - Union Plus / Union Privilege, 2002- (Box 100)
  - Union Reform League, undated (Box 100)
  - Union Sindical Argentina, 1925- (Box 100)
  - Union Theological Seminary (New York, N.Y.), 1940 (Box 129, Folder 27)
  - Union Traction Company (Philadelphia, PA), 1896 (Box 100)
  - Union WAGE (Women's Alliance to Gain Equality), 1973- (Box 100)
  - Union WAGE (Women's Alliance to Gain Equality), 1977-1979 (Box 100)
  - Unione dei Comunisti Italiani (Marsisti-Leninisti), undated (Box 101)
  - Unionists for Democratic Change (Wichita, KS), 1993- (Box 101)
  - Unita del Popolo, circa 1941 (Box 101)
  - Unitarian Fellowship for Social Justice, 1946 (Box 101)
  - United Action, 1971 (Box 101)
  - United Action Campaign Committee, undated (Box 101)
  - United Action Front - 76, 1976 (Box 101)
  - United Association for Labor Education, 2000 (Box 101)
  - United Black Workers, undated (Box 101)
  - United China Relief, undated (Box 101)
  - United Christian Council for Democracy, 1944-1945 (Box 101)
  - United Church Herald, 1966 (Box 101)
  - United Coalition for Angela Davis Day, 1971 (Box 101)
  - United Colored Socialists of America, 1929 (Box 101)
  - United Committee for Political Freedom, undated (Box 101)
  - United Committee of South-Slavic Americans, 1941- (Box 101)
  - United Council of Working Women, 1929- (Box 101)
  - United Defense Committee Against Loyalty Checks, 1949 (Box 101)
  - United Defense to Free Political Prisoners, 1973 (Box 101)
  - United Farmers League, 1934 (Box 101)
  - United Feminist Front, 1980 (Box 101)
  - United for Action, undated (Box 101)
  - United for a Fair Economy, 2000-2004 (Box 101)
  - United for Peace, 2004, undated (Box 101)
  - United for Peace and Justice, 2003-2006, undated (Box 101, Box 129, Folder 28)
  - United Front Anti-Fascist Committee, 1933 (Box 101)
  - United Front Conference Against New Attacks on Labor, 1932 (Box 101)
  - United Front for the Defense of Puerto Rican Political Prisoners, 1970- (Box 101)
  - United Front May Day Arrangements Committee, 1934 (Box 101)
  - United Front May Day Conference, undated (Box 101)
  - United Front of Cairo (Cairo, IL), 1969- (Box 101)
  - United Front Press, 1976-, undated (Box 101)
  - United Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS), 1957 (Box 101)
  - United Hebrew Trades: Division of the Jewish Labor Committee, 2004- (Box 101)
  - United Housing Foundation (New York, NY), 1966- (Box 101)
  - United Independent-Socialist Campaign Committee, 1958- (Box 101)
  - United Jewish Appeal, 1956- (Box 101)
  - United Jewish Appeal of Greater New York, undated (Box 101)
  - United Labor Agency, 1986 (Box 101)
  - United Labor and People's Committee for May Day, 1946- (Box 101)
  - United Labor May Day Committee, 1936- (Box 101)
  - United Labor Party of America, 1949- (Box 101)
  - United Labor Press Association: Industrial Peace Publications, 1923- (Box 101)
  - United Labor Press Committee, 1943 (Box 101)
  - United Labor Rally (Boston, MA), circa 1944 (Box 101)
  - United Labor School for Greater Boston, 1944 (Box 101)
  - United May Day Committee (New York, NY), 1940- (Box 101)
  - United National Anti-War Committee (UNAC), undated (Box 101)
  - United Nations (pamphlet promotion), 1953, undated (Box 101, Box 129, Folder 29)
  - United Neighborhood Houses of New York, 1946, undated (Box 101)
  - United New York Black Radical Congress, 2001 (Box 101)
  - United Prisoners Union, undated (Box 101)
  - United Revolutionary Front, 1975 (Box 101)
  - United Socialist Action Committee, 1951 (Box 101)
  - United Women's Contingent, undated (Box 101)
  - US Campaign to End the Israeli Occupation, 2000- (Box 101)
  - U.S.-China Peoples Friendship Association I, 1974- (Box 101)
  - U.S.-China Peoples Friendship Association II, 1974- (Box 101)
  - U.S. Committee Against Nuclear War, 1983- (Box 101)
  - U.S. Committee for a Democratic Spain, 1975- (Box 101)
  - U.S. Committee to Free the Five Puerto Rican Nationalists, 1977 (Box 101)
  - U.S. Committee for Friendship with the German Democratic Republic, undated (Box 101)
  - U.S. Committee for Justice to Latin American Political Prisoners, 1968, 1971- (Box 101)
  - U.S. Committee for Refugees, 1991 (Box 101)
  - U.S. Committee for the Carabanchel 10, 1973- (Box 101)
    The Carabanchel 10 were Spanish political prisoners.
  - U.S. Committee Inside Spain, 1975 (Box 101)
  - U.S. Committee to Aid the National Liberation Front in South Vietnam, undated (Box 101)